<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.commercial-editor"
       name="Commercial Editor"
       version="0.5.3"
       provider-name="abe-siticompulsi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <!-- Background service: watches playback, clears stale pending marks -->
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
  <!-- Runnable entry point: summons the marking overlay during playback
       (add it to Favourites, or bind RunScript(service.commercial-editor) to a key) -->
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Mark and auto-skip commercials from inside Kodi</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Fix commercial timestamps during playback with a simple on-screen overlay. Verified segments are written to an EDL sidecar file next to the recording, which Kodi auto-skips on the next playback. Optionally seeds from Plex DVR (comskip) draft markers. Requires direct file playback and a writable media source.</description>
    <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <source>https://github.com/abe-siticompulsi/kodi-commercial-editor</source>
    <news>0.5.3 — status/toast labels marquee when the text overflows (labels never focus, so they get scroll=true).
0.5.2 — overlay: arrow-key navigation between button rows; wider mark button (Italian labels fit).
0.5.1 — "Fix this break" now jumps to the detected start for visual verification (nudge, then mark) instead of adopting it unseen — the accept-only-what-you-saw rule covers both boundaries.
0.5.0 — M2: precision nudge row in the overlay (−1s / −0.2s / +1 frame / +0.2s / +1s, live position) and "Fix this break" (adopt a draft's start, re-mark only the end). Draft dedupe is now overlap-based.
0.4.4 — no functional changes: release-pipeline dress rehearsal (script-built package).
0.4.3 — French (fr_FR) and Spanish (es_ES) localisation.
0.4.2 — Italian localisation (it_IT).
0.4.1 — Beat-2 toast: clearer "Go back" label (was "Undo" — nothing was written yet, the button just returns).
0.4.0 — the two beats: landing detector (onPlayBackSeek) fires a Keep/Undo toast for any skip matching a draft; Beat-1 skip offer when PKC is absent. Only an explicit Keep writes the EDL.
0.3.1 — service fetches draft commercial markers automatically at playback start (published to a window property).
0.3.0 — M1 brick 1: Plex bridge (ratingKey resolution via PKC's plex.db, zero-config server+token from PKC settings, draft commercial marker fetch) + 'diag' entry point.
0.2.0 — 'e' shortcut also works in the video OSD; pause-summoned overlay focuses Close.
0.1.0 — M0 scaffold: manual mark → EDL sidecar → auto-skip on next play.</news>
  </extension>
</addon>
